Here's a surprising fact.
If you take your phone number,
it's possible to find another whole number
bigger than zero such that multiplying
the two of these results in an even bigger
number consisting of just ones and zeros.
What's more, if your phone number
happens to end with a 1, 3, 7 or 9,
it's possible to find a product like this where
every single digit in the result is just a 1.
This is part of a series of monthly puzzlers,
and the puzzle for you this month.
is to prove why this is true.
What I like about this is that if you
try to find the appropriate product for
your specific phone number by brute force,
it almost certainly is going to take you
more computation than you have available.
But if you understand the solution here,
there's a way to be smarter about your brute
force such that you actually could find it.